Guide to the Archives of Irish America Vertical File Collection AIA.013
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- W
  - W.E. Jackson & Co., circa 1997-; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - Web-Based Irish and Irish American Businesses, 1996-2000; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - Weddings, 1967-; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - Weekend Trips (Irish-Themed), 1981, 1999; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - Westchester People's Action Coalition, Inc. (WESPAC), undated; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - West Belfast Economic Forum, 2000; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - The Wild Geese (2 folders), 1993-2005; 2 Folders (Box 20)
  - Wood, Ida E., undated; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - The World of Hibernia: promotional literature and mailings, 1995-; 1 folder (Box 20)
- Oversize
  - Album Liners, undated; 1 folder (Box 22)
  - The American Irish Newsletter, Feb 1987-Mar 1987 (Box 22)
  - Art Exhibitions, May 2007 (Box 22)
  - Catholic Diocese: Columban Fathers, Sep 1960 (Box 22)
  - Catholic Diocese: Roman Catholic Diocese of Brooklyn, 1953 (Box 22)
  - Clan Na Gael of Long Island - felt banner, 1928, 1967 (Box 23)
  - Festivals: New York City and New York State, 1989-1995, undated (Box 22)
  - Festivals: United States (outside NYC and Washington D.C.), 1994-1996 (Box 22)
  - Genealogy, undated (Box 22)
  - "If They'd Only Move Old Ireland Over Here" (Poster), undated (Box 22)
  - Illustrated London News: Supplement, Jul 1844; 1 folder (Box 22)
  - The Irish Rebel Theatre, circa 1980 (Box 22)
  - Life Magazine, Nov 1963-Dec 1963; 1 folder (Box 24)
  - Look Magazine, Dec 1962; 1 folder (Box 24)
  - Merchant Advertisement: Shamrock Valencias, Orange County Caifornia (label from a crate?), undated (Box 24)
    Provenance
    Originally in Patrick Daughton Collection AIA 055
  - Moloney, Michael (Mick), Oct 2004 (Box 24)
  - Sheet Music and Lyrics (3 folders) Titles include: The Four Leaf Shamrock of Glenore, I've Got the Blues for the Wearing of the Green, My Wild Irish Rose, All That I Want is in Ireland, Rose of Kilkenny, Kathleen Mavournee n, Soldiers of Erin: The Rallying Song of the Irish Volunteers, The Irish Lads in Blue, I Dreamt that I Dwelt in Marble Halls, undated; 2 Oversize folders (Box 24)
    Scope and Content Note
    Titles include: The Four Leaf Shamrock of Glenore, I've Got the Blues for the Wearing of the Green, My Wild Irish Rose, All That I Want is in Ireland, Rose of Kilkenny, Kathleen Mavourneen, Soldiers of Erin: The Rallying Song of the Irish Volunteers, The Irish Lads in Blue, I Dreamt that I Dwelt in Marble Halls
  - "New York, New York: The Neighborhoods", Nov 1988 (Box 24)
  - New York Post, Aug 2001; 1 folder (Box 24)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Obituaries, 1963-1976; 1 folder (Box 24)
  - O'Dwyer, Paul ( New York News Magazin e article), May 18, 1975 (Box 24)
  - O'Neill's Irish Pictorial, Apr 1859; 1 folder (Box 24)
  - Plan of the Town of Arklow, undated; 1 folder (Box 24)
  - The Provisional Government of the Irish Republic: 50th Anniversary Calendar, 1966; 1 folder (Box 24)
  - "The Riots at New York -- The Rioters Burning and Sacking the Colored Orphan Asylum" from Harper's Weekly, Aug 1, 1863; 1 oversize folder (Box 24)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade Celebration: Official Program, 1964-1987; 1 oversize folder (Box 25)
  - The Saturday Evening Post, Dec 1963; 1 oversize folder (Box 25)
  - Sisters of St. Joseph:"The Flowering Staff: The Story of the First Century of the Congregation of the Sisters of Saint Joseph in the Diocese of Brookly, New York, 1856-1956", 1 folder (Box 25)
  - Small Productions: "Of Pubs and Paradise", Jun 2004 (Box 25)